<resources>
    <string name="app_name">YOGASAN</string>
    <string name="boat_pose">
           Step1:  Sit with your knees bent, feet on the floor. Place your hands behind your knees,\n
                   lift the chest, engaging the back muscles as you inhale\n\n
           Step2:  Engage your inner thighs and draw your lower belly in and up\n\n
           Step3:  Tip back on the back of your sitting bones and lift your feet up to about knee height, toes spread out\n\n
           Step4:  Bring your arms parallel to the floor\n\n
           Step5:  To go further, straighten your legs\n\n
           Step6:  Stay for 2-5 breaths, work up to 10 breaths\n\n
           Step7:  To come out of the pose, on an exhalation bring your feet down, and sit with a straight spine,\n
                   holding on to your legs for a couple of breaths\n\n</string>
    <string name="bow_pose">
           Step1:  Lie on your belly, with your hands by your side, palms facing up\n\n
           Step2:  Bend your knees and take hold of your ankles with your hands\n\n
           Step3:  Press your pubic bone down, draw your lower belly in and up\n\n
           Step4:  On an inhalation, press your ankles in your hands, lifting your chest and thighs\n\n
           Step5:  Slide your shoulder blades down and towards each other to open your chest\n\n
           Step6:  Stay for a few breaths, breathing into your chest and ribs\n\n
           Step7:  On an exhalation, release your ankles, and gently lie down on your belly for a few breaths.\n
    </string>
    <string name="bridge_pose">
           Step1:  Lying on your back, place your feet flat on the floor, a comfortable distance away from the hips\n\n
           Step2:  Place your arms next to the ribcage. You can either bend your elbows 90 degrees,\n
                   so that your fingers are pointing to the ceiling or hold onto the outer edges of your mat\n\n
           Step3:  On an inhalation, press the back of your shoulders and your feet into the floor and lift your hips up\n\n
           Step4:  Press the inner feet down actively and keep the knees from spreading out wide, by engaging the inner thighs\n\n
           Step5:  Lengthen your tailbone, slide your shoulder blades down your back and keep your neck neutral\n\n
           Step6:  You can clasp your hands behind your back Stay for 5 to 15 breaths\n\n
           Step7:  To come out of the pose, release the arms and roll your spine down on an out-breath\n
    </string>
    <string name="chair_pose">
                   From Mountain pose / Tadasana\n
           Step1:  Exhale as you bend your knees and move your hips back as if you were sitting down on a chair.\n
                   Draw your lower abdomen in and up to support your lower back\n\n
           Step2:  Send your hips back rather than your knees forward, so that you can still see your toes\n\n
           Step3:  Inhale as you raise your arms up around your ears and soften your shoulders\n\n
           Step4:  Keep reaching higher, while sitting lower for 5 to 10 breaths\n\n
           Step5:  To come back into in Tadasana, exhale, as you press your feet down to straighten your legs and then\n
                   bring your arms down to your sides.\n
    </string>
    <string name="child_pose">
           Step1:  Sit on your heels and bring your head down to the floor, on stacked fists or a block.\n\n
           Step2:  Arms can be either stretched out to the front, by your side or hands underneath your forehead.\n\n
           Step3:  Hold the pose for 3 to 5 minutes.\n\n
           Step4:  To come out, roll up vertebra by vertebra, head comes up last.\n\n
           Step5:  Sit on your heels for a few moments.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="cobblers_pose">
           Step1:  It is important to have the pelvis in a neutral position, so sitting on stacked blankets etc\n
                   might be necessary to make that happen. When the pelvis is able to tilt forward,\n
                   you can come into the forward bend variation like in the picture. Otherwise,\n
                   hold on to your feet and keep sitting straight up.\n\n
           Step2: In the full pose, the knees are on the floor, but in reality that isn’t happening for a lot of people.\n
                  Accept that your knees can be anywhere from as high as your shoulders to half way down or lower! It’s all ok,\n
                  you will all still get the benefits.\n\n
           Step3: Do not force the knees down in this pose, rather release the head of the thighbones\n
                  (top of the thighbones) to the floor, and let the knees flow, following that action.\n
                  You can stay anywhere from 1-5 minutes in this pose.\n
    </string>
    <string name="cow_pose">
           Step1: Start from all fours - in a tabletop position.\n
                  Your knees under your hips and wrists under your shoulders or slightly forwards of them.\n\n
           Step2: Spread your fingers, root down through the base of the fingers and press your fingers on the mat.\n\n
           Step3: On an inhalation, lower the belly, lift your chest, tailbone pointing up and look up.\n\n
           Step4: Exhale, come back into your neutral tabletop position.\n\n
    </string>
</resources>
